loveroms.com 2018-04-22

# Privacy Policy

We strongly respect your privacy. All information collected at LoveROMs will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, re-used, or rented in any way. Any information we collect, such as operating systems, screen resolution and browser types are used to help make your visit more enjoyable. 

### Information We Collect

If you decide to become a member of this website, we will collect your email and country listed on your account. Your email is used for account notifications and future newsletters if they become available. Your country is used to help us better serve other users in a similar country. 

### Information Sharing

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your information: 

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via e-mail and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Use Of Information

We may use information (whether personal identifying information or not) that we collect about you to: Manage your relationship with us and provide you with customer support. Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others. Communicate with you by e-mail and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties. Cooperate with legal, criminal or regulatory investigations or proceedings. Manage our business. 

### Linked Content

Certain sections of the Site may involve sites which belongs to third parties. We will not and shall not be responsible for that, and any use by the user of the sites belonging to third parties is in his sole responsibility. Therefore, We will not be responsible for actions that occurred at sites belonging to third parties. Moreover, We warn you from sites belonging to third parties and offers the user to read carefully the terms of use of those sites. 

### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us. 

###  Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at: support [at] loveroms.com
